(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-18T01:52:44.804660",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
ミオ！
Mio!
G-A-M-E-R-S
フブキ！
Fubuki!
ミオ！
Mio!
G-A-M-E-R-S
おかゆ！
Okayu!
ころね！
Korone!
ミオ！
Mio!
Are you ready?
フブキ！
Fubuki!
G-A-M-E-R-S
ミオ！
Mio!
G-A-M-E-R-S
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment until the performance begins.
ミオ
Mio!
フブキ
Fubuki!
G-A-M-E-R-S
おかゆ
Okayu!
ころね
Korone!
Are you ready?
Perfect!
G-A-M-E-R-S
ミオ
Mio!
ミオ！
Ｇ・Ａ・Ｍ・Ｅ・Ｒ・Ｓ
G-A-M-E-R-S
おかゆ！
Okayu!
ころね！
Korone!
Are you ready?
ミオ！
Mio!
フブキ！
Fubuki!
Ｇ・Ａ・Ｍ・Ｅ・Ｒ・Ｓ
G-A-M-E-R-S
フブキ！
Fubuki!
ミオ！
Mio!
G-A-M-E-R-S!
おかゆ！
Okayu!
ころね！
Korone!
Are you ready?
ミオしゃ！
Miosha!
G-A-M-E-R-S!
フブキ！
Fubuki!
ミオ！
Mio!
G-A-M-E-R-S!
おかゆ！
Okayu!
ころね
Korone
Are you ready?
おかゆ
Okayu
F-U-B-U-K-I
フブキ
Fubuki
ミオ
Mio
M-I-O
おかゆ
Okayu
ころね
Korone
Are you ready?
Perfect
Hey! Hey!
Are you ready?
ホロライブゲーマーズ！
Hololive GAMERS!
今日もゲームやるぞー！
I'm gonna play games today too!
みんなに会えて嬉しいよー！
I'm so happy to meet you all!
We Are GAMERS!
みんな待ってたー？
Were you all waiting for us?
いっぱい楽しんでいってねー！
Make sure to have lots of fun!
We Are GAMERS!
おっと！狐が通る、超白！
Oops! A fox is passing by, super white!
白黒見ても耳白、白上フブキです！
Even if you look at white and black, my ears are white, I'm Shirakami Fubuki!
突っ込んでちゃ始まらない
Just butting in won't get things started,
君もすこん部に入部しなさい！
so you should join the Sukon-bu too!
はい、フレンド！ はい、フレンド！
Yes, friend! Yes, friend!
ぽぽんっとお茶ちょうだい！
Pop, pop, give me some tea!
お茶じゃない！得意はFPS！
It's not tea! My specialty is FPS!
赤い太陽より、狐火が青ーい！
Fox-fire is bluer than the red sun!
うち、うち、うちだよ！大神ミオだよ！
It's me, me, me! I'm Ookami Mio!
黒髪ケモ耳、おおかみ！
Black hair, beast ears, a wolf!
突っ込んで骨までしゃぶります
I'm diving in to suck you dry to the bone,
タロットカード！笑い出すと止まらない、ゲラゲラ！
tarot cards! Once I start laughing, I can't stop, haha!
つまりポンコツはウソってこと？
So, does that mean being clumsy is a lie?
おかしセンス、少しオコ？
A weird sense of humor, are you a bit miffed?
タロット占いでみる未来、ほらゲームやりたくなーい！
Reading the future with tarot cards, look, don't you want to play a game?!
4人揃えばかしまし大騒ぎ
When the four of us get together, it's a noisy racket.
君も遊ぼうよ Bダッシュ
You play with us too, B-Dash!
クリア目指して レベルアップ
Aiming for the clear, level up!
今日は何プレイしよう？
What shall we play today?
君のハートも攻略しちゃう
We'll even capture your heart.
選択をして シミュレーション
Choose your options, simulation!
初見も古参も大歓迎
First-timers and veterans are all very welcome!
ヨソはヨソ！うちのゲームは楽しいね！
Others are others! Our games are fun, right?!
G-A-M-E-R-S
We Are GAMERS!
胃袋もぐもぐ、眠くなったらおやすみ
Munching food, when you get sleepy, good night.
おにぎりおにぎり、はいどうぞ
Onigiri, onigiri, here you go!
きらきらふわふわ、しょうがない猫だもん
Twinkling and fluffy, well, I'm just a cat after all.
ねえ、もっと構ってくれてもよくない？
Hey, shouldn't you pay more attention to me?
まったりゆっくり、流れるリズム
Relaxed and slowly, a flowing rhythm.
全肯定するよ、肯定リズム
I approve of everything, the approval rhythm.
全肯定コール、オッケー？
All-approval call, okay?
毎日僕と生きよう
Live with me every day.
おらよー！ 指、指、指わおーん！
Here you go! Fingers, fingers, fingers, woof!
パンをこねこね、犬神ころね！
Kneading bread, Inugami Korone!
チェーンソー、バリア、金属バット
Chainsaw, barrier, metal bat!
スーパーリアルな味付けだけど、暑苦しくて！
Super realistic seasoning, but it's stuffy!
訛るイントネーション、割れるリアクション
Accented intonation, loud reaction.
まずは指を捧げてくれる？ 配信開始！
First, will you offer your fingers? Stream start!
骨、骨、骨、骨、骨、オッケー？
Bone, bone, bone, bone, bone, okay?
好物のレトロゲーム、おどけけ！
My favorite retro games, let's play!
4人揃えばかしまし大騒ぎ
When the four of us get together, it's a noisy racket.
フラグ立てれば即回収
Triggering flags, and immediately resolving them.
夢を競って メロメロに
Competing in dreams, falling head over heels.
今日は何プレイしよう？
What shall we play today?
君のハートを回復しちゃう
We'll restore your heart.
ワクワクするね この感情
Getting excited, this feeling.
耐久ゲーム いざ参る！
Endurance game, here we come!
やめられない だって
We can't stop because...
ゲームが好きなんだもん
we just love games!
突然ですが、ボーナスチャレンジの時間です！
All of a sudden, it's time for the Bonus Challenge!
大きな声でレスポンスをして、高得点を狙いましょう！
Respond with a loud voice and let's aim for a high score!
Are you ready? せーの！
Are you ready? One, two, go!
コーン！コーン！
Kon! Kon!
ミョーン！ミョーン！
Myon! Myon!
もぐ！もぐ！
Mogu! Mogu!
指！指！
Yubi! Yubi!
コーン！コーン！
Kon! Kon!
ミョーン！ミョーン！
Myon! Myon!
もぐ！もぐ！
Mogu! Mogu!
指！指！
Yubi! Yubi!
Perfect! おー！
Perfect! Oh!
4人揃えばかしまし大騒ぎ
When the four of us get together, it's a noisy racket.
うまく行かなくたって コンティニュー
Even if it doesn't go well, continue!
クリアするまで 諦めない
We won't give up until we clear it!
エンディングは 観に行こう
Let's go see the ending!
君のハートも 攻略しちゃう
We'll capture your heart too.
選択をして シミュレーション
Choose your options, simulation!
初見も古参も大歓迎
First-timers and veterans are all very welcome!
ヨソはヨソ！うちのゲームは楽しいね！
Others are others! Our games are fun, right?!
G-A-M-E-R-S
We are GAMERS!
こうして、さいたまスーパーアリーナに平和が訪れたのであった！
And thus, peace returned to Saitama Super Arena!
はい、ということで始まりました！
Alright, and with that, we have begun!
ホロライブゲーマーズフェス 超超超超ゲーマーズ2です！
It's Hololive Gamers Fes, Chou Chou Chou Chou Gamers 2!
はい、じゃあちょっとね、自己紹介やっていきますかね。
Alright, shall we start with some self-introductions?
皆さん、こんこんきーつね！
Everyone, Konkon-kitsune!
白上フブキです！よろしくお願いします！
I'm Shirakami Fubuki! Nice to meet you all!
そしてそしてね、もう1曲目ちょっとね、あのー、『We Are Gamers』やらせてもらったんですけども、
And also, we just performed our first song, 'We Are Gamers'...
ついにね、4人ということで、いるじゃないですか、赤いのが！
But now, all four of us are here, including that red one over there!
さあ！さあ！
Come on! Come on!
はい！うち！うち！うちだよ！
Yes! Me! Me! It's me!
大神ミオ･･･あれ？違ったっけ？
Ookami Mio... Wait, did I get that wrong?
あ、おおかみみおの皆さん、いらっしゃいませー！
Ah, welcome, everyone of Ookami Mio!
違うんだよ！おかしいんだよな！
That's wrong! That's so weird!
はい、続いて！
Alright, next up!
もぐもぐ、おかゆー！
Mogu mogu, Okayu!
はい、どうも！猫又おかゆです！
Yes, hello! I'm Nekomata Okayu!
今日はね、最高な思い出を作って、楽しんじゃいましょう！
Let's make the best memories today and have lots of fun!
はい！ゆー！びー！ゆーびー！
Yes! Yu! Bi! Yubi, yubi!
戌神ころねです！みんな今日は、大事な日なの。何の日か知ってる？
I'm Inugami Korone! Today is an important day, everyone. Do you know what day it is?
今日はね、大谷翔平の誕生日！
Today is Shohei Ohtani's birthday!
ということで、戌神ころねです、よろしくお願いします！
So, I'm Inugami Korone. Nice to meet you all!
ということでね、改めて、4人揃って、揃ってます！
And so, once again, all four of us... we're all here!
ホロライブゲーマーズフェス 超超超超ゲーマーズ2、そのDay 1がここ、さいたまスーパーアリーナで開催でございます！
Hololive Gamers Fes, Chou Chou Chou Chou Gamers 2 Day 1 is now being held here at Saitama Super Arena!
そして、なんとですね、あの、Day 1、Day 2、両席とも完売ということで！
And incredibly, Day 1 and Day 2 are both completely sold out!
すごいんです！なんと、Day 1、Day 2、ともに約、1万･･･なんか、5000とか7000とかのファンの皆さんが今日、来てくださってる。そうです！
It's amazing! For both Day 1 and Day 2, about 15,000 or 17,000 fans have come to see us today! That's right!
運営さんから、Day 1、Day 2合わせて3万2000人くらいですって！
According to the staff, it's about 32,000 people total for Day 1 and Day 2!
やばすぎる！すごすぎる！ほぼ人間じゃん！
This is crazy! Too amazing! It's almost all humans!
ほぼ人間だよね。
Almost all humans, right?
ほぼ人間だよ、人間以外、誰がいるんだよ！
Almost humans? Who else would be here besides humans?!
ね、1回目はね、あの、国立代々木競技場 第一体育館だったんですけども、今回はさいたまスーパーアリーナということで！
Well, our first event was at the Yoyogi National Stadium First Gymnasium, but this time we're at the Saitama Super Arena!
すごいですよね！ありがとうございます！
Isn't that amazing? Thank you so much!
さて、改めて、このイベントはですね、ゲームが大好きな我々ゲーマーズを中心に、超・超・超・超豪華な･･･
Now, once again, this event is a premium event centered around us Gamers who love games, with super-super-super-super-gorgeous...
ちょっと『超』多かったかな？
Wait, did I say 'super' too many times?
ゲストと一緒に、色々なゲームタイトルに挑戦したり、ライブパフォーマンスをお届けするプレミアムイベントです！
...guests, where we challenge various game titles and deliver live performances!
しかも今回、皆さんね、あの、突然出てきて「え？3Dなの？」って感じなんですけど、4人のお揃いの衣装、お披露目でございます！
Moreover, we suddenly appeared like 'Wait, is it 3D?', but we are also revealing our matching outfits today!
はい、ね、本当に、この衣装可愛いから「着たいね！」って言ってたら、用意してくださいました。ありがとうございます。
Yes, we really thought these outfits were so cute and wanted to wear them, and they prepared them for us. Thank you so much.
いや、もう本当に可愛いですよね。ありがとうございます。
Yeah, they really are so cute. Thank you so much.
さらにですね、会場では一部、撮影OKのパートがありますので！そちらではですね、あの、スマホでお写真を撮っていただけると嬉しいです。
Furthermore, there is a designated part of the venue where photography is allowed! In that part, we'd be delighted if you could take photos with your smartphones.
ぜひ最後まで一緒に楽しみましょう！
Let's enjoy this together until the very end!
ということでね、始まっていくんですけども、1人ずつちょっと、意気込み、お願いしたいと思いますよ。じゃあまずは、ミオから！
So, we're about to get started, but first, I'd like to ask each of us for our determination. Let's start with Mio!
はい！
Yes!
今年は、去年はね、ちょっとお休みしちゃったんですけど
This year... well, last year we took a break, but
今年は4人でね、無事に開催することができたので
this year, the four of us safely held this,
えー、明日も無事に終えられるように
so to ensure tomorrow goes smoothly as well,
体調管理だけはしっかりして、2日間過ごしたいと思います！頑張るぞー！
I'll manage my health well for these two days! Let's do our best!
頑張るぞー！
Let's do our best!
はーい！
Okay!
ではでは、続いては？おかゆ！
Now then, next up is... Okayu!
はーい！
Hi!
ま、僕はね、去年、引き続きの参加となるんですが
Well, for me, I'm participating again following last year,
ま、今日はね、大谷翔平の誕生日ということで
but today is Shohei Ohtani's birthday...
せやな、せやな、大谷関係ないけど！
Yeah, that's true, though Ohtani has nothing to do with this!
そう、関係ないけどさ
Yeah, it has nothing to do with it, but...
なので、野手打率3割目指して頑張りたいと思います！
so I'll do my best aiming for a .300 batting average!
ちょっと待って！打率3割？
Wait a minute! A .300 batting average?
3割でいいの？ / おかゆならもっといけそうだけどな
Is .300 enough? / I feel like Okayu could do even better.
いやいやいや
No, no, no.
そして？
And next?
はい！
Yes!
今日はね、翔平に素敵なパフォーマンスを
Today, I want to deliver a wonderful performance to Shohei
届けられるように頑張るぞー！
so that it reaches him! Let's do this!
翔平に届く？ロサンゼルスに届く？
Reach Shohei? All the way to Los Angeles?
ロサンゼルスに届けます！
I'll send it all the way to Los Angeles!
イェーイ！ / そして、そして？
Yay! / And next?
はい！白上フブキはですね、皆さん、
Yes! As for me, Shirakami Fubuki,
昨年に続きまして、なんと台本の8割を白上が読み上げるということで！
following last year, I'll be reading about 80% of the script!
なので、声が枯れないように、喉のケアに気をつけつつ、
So, to keep my voice from giving out, I'll take care of my throat
台本を読み上げたいと思います！
and read through the script!
なので、かすれ始めたら、「頑張ってるな」と思って、ペンライトを振ってください！
So if my voice starts crackling, please wave your penlights to support me!
お願いします！
Please do!
お前らの声に負けねえからな！よろしく！
I'll not let your voices beat mine! Let's go!
イェーイ！
Yay!
はい！そしてですね、今日と明日行われる「超超超超ゲーマーズ2」は
Yes! And the "Chochochocho GAMERS 2" happening today and tomorrow
ABEMA PPVで生配信してます！見ている？
is being live-streamed on ABEMA PPV! Are you watching?
見てるー！見てるよー！
We're watching! We see you!
コメントもね、我々見えておりますよ！
We can see your comments too!
ねえ、ありがとうございます！
Yes, thank you very much!
こちら、配信チケットは絶賛発売中です！
The stream tickets are currently on sale!
イベントが終わっても、8月4日月曜日の23時59分まで
Even after the event ends, until Monday, August 4th at 23:59,
何度でも見返すことができます！
you can watch the archive as many times as you want!
おおー！素晴らしい！
Oh! Wonderful!
購入特典としましては、Day 1とDay 2で異なるシチュエーションの
As a purchase bonus, Day 1 and Day 2 feature different situations
限定オリジナルボイスドラマがついてきます！
for the exclusive original voice drama!
Day 1は「秘密の事前プロデュースボイス」！
Day 1 is "Secret Pre-Production Voice"!
秘密？これ、エッチなやつ？ / エッチなやつかな？
Secret? Is this something naughty? / Is it naughty?
違います！
No, it's not!
そして、Day 2は「内緒の超打ち上げボイス」！
And Day 2 is "Secret Post-Event Celebration Voice"!
これ、エッチなやつかな？ / やめな！
Is this one naughty? / Stop it!
こちらのボイス、エッチじゃないです！普通に聴いてください！
These voices are not naughty! Please just listen normally!
あとはですね、我々の直筆メッセージ入りのライブ画像もついてきますので
Also, it comes with a live image featuring our handwritten messages,
ぜひチェックしてください！
so please check it out!
さらに！
Furthermore!
昨年行われました「超超超超ゲーマーズ」の
the digest video of last year's "Chochochocho GAMERS"
ダイジェストがABEMAプレミアムで公開中です！
is currently available on ABEMA Premium!
昨年のものもね、めちゃめちゃ面白かったので、ぜひとも見てください！
Last year's event was super fun too, so please watch it!
お願いします！
Please do!
さらにさらに！イベント後にグッズの受注販売が開始します！
And furthermore, pre-orders for the event goods will start after the event!
ありがたいことに、Day 1のグッズが完売らしくて！
Gratefully, it seems Day 1 goods are already sold out!
皆さんありがとうございます！
Thank you so much, everyone!
ありがとう！みんな！
Thank you, everyone!
こちら、グッズの受注販売の期間は、本日の朝10時から
The pre-order period for these goods starts today at 10:00 AM
7月21日の23時59分まで
until July 21st at 23:59
Cyber Goods Storeにて受付中でございます！
on the Cyber Goods Store!
こちらのグッズ、9月下旬までにはお届け予定とのことです！
These goods are scheduled to be delivered by late September!
おおー！なるほど
Oh, I see!
そしてなんと！事後限定グッズとして
And surprisingly, as post-event exclusive goods,
アクリルパネルが追加されます！
an acrylic panel will be added!
イベント限定グッズが手に入る最後のチャンスなので、ぜひぜひチェックしてください！
This is your last chance to get event-exclusive goods, so make sure to check it out!
イェーイ！
Yay!
先生の話をおとなしく聞けない生徒みたいになってます
We look like students who can't quietly listen to the teacher.
聞いてるよ！ / でも、みおも...
We are listening! / But Mio too...
混ざって。先生話すからね！
We got mixed up. The teacher is going to speak!
はーい！
Okay!
さらにさらに！もうご存知の方もいらっしゃるかと思いますが
And furthermore! As some of you may already know,
NTTドコモさんの「home 5G」との
our collaboration with NTT Docomo's "home 5G"
コラボキャンペーンも実施してまーす！
campaign is also underway!
イェーイ！
Yay!
先生の話は聞かなくてもいいけど、声は出さないで！
You don't have to listen to the teacher, but please keep your voices down!
すみません
Sorry...
NTTドコモさんのご紹介してたでしょう！
I was introducing NTT Docomo!
はい！どうぞ！
Yes! Go ahead!
お友達か！
Are we friends or what?!
入り口でもらえるうちわ、皆さんゲットしましたか？
Did everyone get the hand fan given out at the entrance?
もらった方！
Those who got one?
おお！ありがとうございます！
Oh! Thank you very much!
もらったうちわも使って、熱中症対策を万全にして、
Please use those fans to make sure you prevent heatstroke,
最後まで楽しんでください！
and enjoy the show until the very end!
熱中症対策はね。
練習しよ、練習。
We need to be careful of heatstroke.
Let's practice, practice.
まだまだ続きますよ。
There's still more to come!
超ゲマズ２、我々ゲマズを応援したいという声が多かったので、
Since so many of you wanted to support Gamers at Cho Gamers 2,
今回イベントでチアスポット様とコラボすることが決定しました！
we've decided to collaborate with CheerSPOT for this event!
誰でも簡単に、
Anyone can easily...
好きなチアスポットの場所に、白上達、ゲマズの応援広告を出すことができます！
place support ads for Shirakami and Gamers at their favorite CheerSPOT locations!
おお、すごい！すごい！
Oh, that's amazing! Great!
会場内にもね、これ、あの、なんと、
And even inside the venue, actually,
スポットが我々になってまして、びっくりしました。
there are spots featuring us, which really surprised me.
そうなんです。見てないの？
That's right. Haven't you seen them?
見てたよ！見てた！
見てた、見てた。
I saw them! I saw them!
We saw them!
そう、そう、そう。
Yes, indeed, indeed.
気になる方はね、会場内に確かあったと思いますので、よかったら見てください。
If you're curious, they should be inside the venue, so please check them out.
そしてさらに、さいたまスーパーアリーナ会場内で、等身大を初お披露目！
And furthermore, inside Saitama Super Arena, we're debuting our life-sized figures!
３月のエキスポ会場で発表されましたフブミオ等身大に続きまして、
Following the FubuMio life-sized figures announced at the Expo in March,
おかころのフィギュアもお披露目され、４人揃ってお披露目となりました！
the OkaKoro figures are also on display, so all four of us are now shown together!
事前の告知配信ではさ、なかったらあの、おかちゃんとお宝なんじゃないかって言ったんですけど、ちゃんと揃ってました。
In the pre-announcement stream, we joked that Okayu and Korone's figures might not be ready, but they are both here!
揃ってましたね。めちゃめちゃ可愛かったです。
They really are. They were super cute.
ありがとうございます。そしてまた、本日から、
Thank you. And also, starting today,
新作のフィギュアがデザインココ様から受注開始です！
pre-orders for new figures from Design COCO have begun!
可愛い！
So cute!
イベント開催を記念して、8月7日までにココストアで予約してくれた方には、特典のステッカーをプレゼントされるそうです！
To commemorate the event, those who pre-order on COCO Store by August 7th will receive a special bonus sticker!
可愛い！
How cute!
やっぱりね、白上とミオも欲しいなという、そう思った、
And for those of you who also want Shirakami and Mio's figures,
そこにいる、あなた！あなた！あなた！
yes, you! You! You over there!
なんと、超ゲマズ２の開催を記念して、期間限定で、フブミオ追加予約を開始です！
To celebrate Cho Gamers 2, we are launching additional pre-orders for FubuMio for a limited time!
「逃したよ」っていうのもね、何人かエゴサで見かけましたので、これを機会にぜひともご予約お願いします。
I saw some comments online saying "I missed it," so please take this opportunity to pre-order!
お願いします！
Please do!
そして最後に、カンダフル様による、協賛企業グッズ、
And finally, sponsor goods from Kandaful,
超超超超ポップコーンと超超超超グリルチキンのご紹介でございます。
introducing the "Cho-Cho-Cho-Cho Popcorn" and "Cho-Cho-Cho-Cho Grilled Chicken"!
今回のイベントのキービジュアルが前面に出たデザインとなっているとのことです。
They feature a design showcasing the event's key visual on the front.
ポップコーンは税込み1000円で、チキンは税込み1500円での販売でございます。
The popcorn is 1,000 yen (tax incl.), and the chicken is 1,500 yen (tax incl.).
ポップコーンは塩キャラメル味、チキンはグリルチキン味になってます。
The popcorn is salted caramel flavor, and the chicken is grilled chicken flavor.
トレカも付いてる。
そう、トレカも付いてます。
They come with trading cards too.
Yes, they also come with trading cards.
こちらのグッズは他のグッズと異なり、受注生産ではなく、数量限定商品のため、
Unlike our other merchandise, these are not made-to-order but are limited in quantity,
急いでください！
so please hurry!
集合アクリルパネルも含めて、事後でしか購入できないグッズですので、皆さんぜひご確認ください。
These items, including the group acrylic panel, can only be purchased afterward, so please check them out.
お願いします！
Please do!
なんと、なんと、ちなみに今回、韓国でライブビューイングもやってるそうですよ！
And, believe it or not, they are also hosting a live viewing in Korea!
韓国の皆さん、アンニョンハセヨ！
Everyone in Korea, annyeonghaseyo!
アンニョンハセヨ！
Annyeonghaseyo!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ではですね、色々ご紹介も終わりましたので、早速、
Now that we've gone through all the announcements, let's...
最初に。行うゲームタイトル、発表しちゃいましょう！
announce our very first game title!
始めちゃうの？
Are we starting already?
いきますよ！せーの、こちら！
Here we go! Ready, set, go... This is it!
ビビッター！
Bibitter!
こちらルールは超簡単！
The rules for this are super simple!
ミニゲームに対し、タイミングよくボタンを押して、ギリギリで止めるだけ！
Just press the button with the right timing during the minigame and stop it right at the limit!
なるほど。
I see.
我々のですね、度胸を試す、究極のビビリチェッカーゲームとなっております！
It's the ultimate test of courage to check how easily we get scared!
よりギリギリを攻めると、クールの評価がもらえるそうです。
If you stop closer to the limit, you'll receive a "Cool" rating.
今回ですね、我々、個人戦でございます。
We will be competing individually today!
１つのミニゲームに対し、２人がそれぞれ挑戦します。
For each minigame, two of us will take turns challenging it.
様々な組み合わせで、合計６ゲーム楽しんでいただきたいと思います。
We will play a total of six games with various combinations.
こちらですね、我々のクールの合計数で、１位を決めたいと思いますので、よろしくお願いします。
We'll decide the winner based on the total number of "Cool" ratings, so wish us luck.
ではですね、ゲームを始める前に、
So, before we start the game...
なんと今回ですね、巨大コントローラーを用意してくれたということで、
...they have prepared a giant controller for us!
召喚しましょう！
Let's summon it!
これでちょっと、会場の皆さんも一緒に、「出でよ、巨大コントローラー」とね、叫んでくれると嬉しいです。
I'd love for everyone in the venue to shout along with us, "Appear, Giant Controller!"
あー！
Oh!
いでよ！巨大コントローラー！
Come forth! Giant controller!
いでよ、巨大コントローラー、ですね。
"Come forth, giant controller," indeed.
ここに、ここに来ますからね、皆さん、行きますよ。
It's coming right here! Everyone, here we go!
せーの！
Ready, set...
いでよ、巨大コントローラー！
Come forth, giant controller!
おー！出たー！
Whoa! It appeared!
すごい！可愛い！
Amazing! So cute!
出た、出た！
I pressed it! I pressed it!
すごーい！可愛い！
Amazing! This is so cute!
すごい、ちゃんと我々のマークになっている。
Wow, it has all of our respective symbols on it!
可愛いー！
So cute!
では、どの順番でチャレンジしていきますか？
Now then, in what order should we challenge it?
我こそはという人！
Anyone who wants to go first?
我こそは？我こそは、は？
Anyone? Anyone?
じゃあ、でも、ミオしゃじゃない？やっぱり。
Well, shouldn't it be Mio-sha, after all?
おお！おかえり！そうだよ、ミオしゃおかえり！お帰り！そうだよ、ミオしゃお帰り！
Oh! Welcome back! That's right, welcome back, Mio-sha!
やった方がいいって、ミオしゃ。
You should definitely do it, Mio-sha!
やったー！そうだ、ミオしゃ！
Yeah! That's right, Mio-sha!
わー！じゃあ、ミオしゃ１位、ミオで。
Wow! Okay, so Mio-sha is first. Mio.
続いてはどうする？二人目。
What about next? The second person.
二人目やりたい？
Do you want to go second?
やりたい！やりたい？おかゆ２番目？
I want to! You do? Okayu second?
ごめん、ごめん。おいで、おいで。
Wait, wait. Come here.
じゃ、おかゆ２番目。
Okay, Okayu second.
じゃあ、おかゆ２番目。
Then Okayu is second.
流れ的にね。
Going with the flow.
３番目はどうする？
What about the third person?
３番目？これ、どっちがいい？
Third? Which of you wants to go?
いや、トリは嫌だ。
No, I don't want to go last.
３番手！おー！
Third! Oh!
自由な仕切りだな〜
Such a free-spirited way of organizing~
ということで、対戦順決まりました。一番最初はミオ、おかゆ。
So the order is decided. First is Mio, then Okayu.
はい、ミオとおかゆの対戦になります。お〜！
Yes, it'll be Mio vs Okayu. Oh!
ということで、じゃあ、本番やっていきましょう。
So let's start the real match.
ミオちゃんさ、僕が勝っても泣かないでね。
Mio-chan, don't cry even if I win, okay?
おかゆには何度も負かされてきてるし。
I've been defeated by Okayu many times before.
この猫めちゃくちゃミニゲーム強いんですよ！
This cat is crazy good at mini-games!
そう、ちょっと強いよね。強すぎるまである。
Yeah, she's pretty strong. Too strong, even.
このゲームは初見だからさ。
But this is our first time playing this game.
適性が高すぎるんだって、ミニゲームの。
Her aptitude for mini-games is just too high.
確かにそれはあるかも。
True, that might be a thing.
だから、そこでうちが勝ったら、めっちゃ奇跡的なことでしょ？
So if I win there, it would be a total miracle, right?
奇跡起こしちゃう？起こしちゃおう！
Are you going to make a miracle happen? Let's do it!
ええ〜
Whoa~
それじゃあ、やっていきますか！はーい！
Well then, shall we start? Yes!
色んなゲームがあるんですけど、まずは「試練の２」というものを...
There are various games, but first, "Trial 2"...
やっていこうかなと思います。
...is what I think we should do.
これ、スタッフさんがやったんですけど、スタッフさんが強すぎる。
The staff tried this earlier, but they were too strong.
確かに、スタッフがちょっと...
True, the staff was a bit...
じゃ、準備はいいですか？ミオ。はい！
So, are you ready, Mio? Yes!
それでは行きますよ。ミオちゃんのビビりタス、スタート！
Here we go. Mio-chan's Viviri Trial, start!
あちらのお客様から、グラスを滑らせよう。
Slide the glass to the customer over there.
お、お！あちらのお客様からグラスを滑らせる。
Oh! Slide the glass to that customer over there.
ほうほう。マスター、あちらの美しい女性に一杯。
I see. Master, a drink for that beautiful lady.
かしこまりました。
Certainly.
何だこいつの顔！
Look at this guy's face!
クリックすると？まず練習ですね。
What happens when you click? First is practice, right?
練習、はい。グラスを滑らせろ。
Practice, yes. Slide the glass.
いきます！
Here I go!
左にゲージがある。
There's a gauge on the left.
長押しして、ゲージを貯めるらしい。お！ちょっと行きすぎたかな？
Hold to fill the gauge. Did it go too far?
え？もう１回いけないんですか？
Eh? Can't we try one more time?
本番！本番、いきます！
Real deal! Real deal, here I go!
いきます！
Here I go!
ここだ！お！
Here! Oh!
お〜！すごい！
Oh! Amazing!
すごいすごい！
Amazing, amazing!
何そのポーズ？ビクトリーポーズ！
What's with that pose? Victory pose!
真ん中でやりたかった！
I wanted to do it in the middle!
ちょっと早かった。
It was a bit too early.
ということで、ミオは今、５０だったかな？
So, Mio is at 50 now?
５０だね。ということで、続いてはおかゆなんですけど、どうですか？
50, yeah. Next is Okayu, how about you?
いけますか？自信あり？
Can you do it? Confident?
頑張ります。
I'll do my best.
それでは行きますよ、おかゆのビビりタス、スタート！
Then here we go. Okayu's Viviri Trial, start!
あちらのお客様から、グラスを滑らせよう。
Slide the glass to the customer over there.
あちらのお客様からグラスを滑らせる。
Slide the glass from that customer over there.
マスター、あちらの美しい女性にこれと同じものを。
Master, the same as that one for the beautiful lady.
かしこまりました。
Certainly.
クリックお願いします。
Click, please.
練習！お、練習ね、まず。
Practice! Oh, practice first, right.
いけるか？
Can you do it?
え？え？
Eh? Eh?
自分の注文じゃねえかそれ！
Isn't that your own order?!
やばい、本番になっちゃった！本番だよ！
Oh no, it started for real! It's the real deal!
頑張れ！
Do your best!
あ、の、の、残し...！
Ah, I-I-I left some...!
残した！
I left some!
あ、やば！
Ah, oh no!
お、K.O.だ！
Oh, it's a K.O.!
なんで？ なんで？ なんて言いました？
Why? Why? What did you say?
おかゆちゃん！
Okayu-chan!
そんなお尻フリフリで勝てるわけないじゃん！
There's no way you can win by shaking your butt like that!
勝てるわけないだろ！
Of course you can't win!
勝てるわけないからね！
There's no way you can win!
これで勝てませんかね？ 今の...
Can't we win with that? Just now...
負け！
You lost!
なわけないだろー！
No way!
強いなー！
So strong!
みおちゃん強かった！
Mio-chan was so strong!
これ、無双できそうだね、これね
Looks like we can totally dominate this!
よねー！
Right?!
うそー！
No way!
ということで、皆様、こちら突然ではございますが、お知らせでございます！
And so, everyone, this is very sudden, but we have an announcement!
なんと、無料配信をご覧の皆様は、ここまでとなります！
Believe it or not, this is the end for those watching the free stream!
えぇー！
Eeh?!
続きをご覧になりたい方は、ぜひABEMA PPVにて、チケットの購入をお願いします！
If you want to watch the rest, please purchase a ticket on ABEMA PPV!
お願いしまーす！
Please do!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
おつくりー！ バイバイなー！
Thanks for watching! Bye-bye!
ね、これからもね、あの、めちゃめちゃ楽しいゲーム、ね、ゲストもいるのでね
You know, from here on, we have super fun games, and guests too!
はい！
Yes!
楽しんでいただけると思います。よろしくお願いします！
I'm sure you will enjoy it. Thank you!
よろしくお願いしまーす！
Thank you!
それでは！
With that!
見に来てねー！
Come watch, okay!
まったねー！
See you!
フゥー！
Woo!
無料パートは終了いたしました 全編はABEMA PPVにて視聴可能！
[Text: The free part has ended. Watch the full broadcast on ABEMA PPV!]
無料パートは終了いたしました
全編はABEMA PPVにて視聴可能！
[The free portion of this stream has ended.
The full event is available to watch on ABEMA PPV!]
配信の詳細はQRコードをチェック！
[Check the QR code for streaming details!]
豪華購入特典：オリジナルボイスドラマと
限定直筆メッセージ入りライブ画像がもらえる！
[Bonus: Original voice drama & limited live photo
with a handwritten message!]
G-A-M-E-R-S
ミオ！
Mio!
おかゆ！
Okayu!
G-A-M-E-R-S
ころね！
Korone!
フブキ！
Fubuki!
ゲーマーズ！
Gamers!
無料パートは終了いたしました
The free portion of the event has ended.
全編はABEMA PPVにて視聴可能！
The full show is available on ABEMA PPV!
配信の詳細はQRコードをチェック！
Scan the QR code for streaming details!
購入特典：オリジナルボイスドラマ＆限定直筆メッセージ入りライブ画像
Bonus: Original voice drama & special photo!
無料パートは終了いたしました
The free portion of the event has ended.
全編はABEMA PPVにて視聴可能！
The full show is available on ABEMA PPV!
配信の詳細はQRコードをチェック！
Scan the QR code for streaming details!
購入特典：オリジナルボイスドラマ＆限定直筆メッセージ入りライブ画像
Bonus: Original voice drama & special photo!
無料パートは終了いたしました
The free portion of the event has ended.
全編はABEMA PPVにて視聴可能！
The full show is available on ABEMA PPV!
配信の詳細はQRコードをチェック！
Scan the QR code for streaming details!
購入特典：オリジナルボイスドラマ＆限定直筆メッセージ入りライブ画像
Bonus: Original voice drama & special photo!
無料パートは終了いたしました
The free portion of the event has ended.
全編はABEMA PPVにて視聴可能！
The full show is available on ABEMA PPV!
配信の詳細はQRコードをチェック！
Scan the QR code for streaming details!
購入特典：オリジナルボイスドラマ＆限定直筆メッセージ入りライブ画像
Bonus: Original voice drama & special photo!
無料パートは終了いたしました
The free portion of the event has ended.
全編はABEMA PPVにて視聴可能！
The full show is available on ABEMA PPV!
配信の詳細はQRコードをチェック！
Scan the QR code for streaming details!
購入特典：オリジナルボイスドラマ＆限定直筆メッセージ入りライブ画像
Bonus: Original voice drama & special photo!
無料パートは終了いたしました
全編はABEMA PPVにて視聴可能！
The free portion of the broadcast has ended.
The full event is available on ABEMA PPV!
配信の詳細はQRコードをチェック！
Scan the QR code for more details!